Alesia G. Junior Software Engineer

Intetics, Inc. 10001 Tamiami Trail N, Suite 114 Naples, FL 34108 Tel: +1 (877) 763-8338

Tel: +1 (877) 763-8338 Email: contact@intetics.com



CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

► Experience in creating Branded Job Templates using the design provided by client or without it

Front-end developer with experience in creating responsive user interfaces.

Overview: Front-end developer with experience in creating responsive websites from scratch and also from mockups.

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

- ▶ Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript
- ▶ Technologies: SASS, LESS, Angular, jQuery
- Frameworks and Libraries: Bootstrap 3,4
- ▶ Development Environments (IDE)/Tools: Webstorm, IntelliJ IDEA, VS Code
- ▶ Operation Systems/Platforms: Windows, GitHub

EXPERIENCE

INTETICS INC. - Minsk, Belarus

Jun 2018 — Present

Junior Software Engineer (Jun 2018 — Jun 2019), Software Engineer (Jun 2019 — Present)

Representative Development Projects:

▶ efinancialcareers

The world's leading financial services careers website

Responsibilities: - Creating new features and support of existing

- Recommending design solutions for better UX
- Bugfixing
- Client communication
- Working in team using SCRUM methodology
- Designing and implementing HTML branded templates

Technologies and Tools: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, LESS, Angular, JavaScript, Git, Adobe Photoshop, Zeplin

Project Size: 10 developers, 2 QA, Tech lead, Project Manager

LANGUAGES

English Upper-intermediate Polish Intermediate

EDUCATION

BSU Minsk, Belarus

Bachelor's Degree Translator linguist

Disclaimer: Intetics shall accept no liability whether on its own behalf, or on behalf of its staff, for any loss or damage costs or expenses whatsoever, arising directly or indirectly or in connection with any act or omission of applicant supplied or referred by it., You will ensure that your employees, representative or agent will not copy, reproduce, utilize, exploit or in any other manner whatsoever use any

Alesia G. | Page 2 Continued



information contained herein for any purpose other than is necessary for the evaluation of resume. Any of the information contained herein can be communicated to any person, firm, corporation, association or any entity for the same purpose of evaluating the resume but only with the consent of Intetics. Within a period of one (1) year, should the applicant named herein is engaged by you or by another party to whom you have introduced the said applicant, then you will be liable for the appropriate service fee plus damages for breach of confidence.,Nothing in this transmission imposes on either party an obligation to enter into any agreement or transaction and in particular will not oblige either party to enter into any agreement pursuant to the Business Proposed.